Guide to the Paul Ehrlich Papers SC0223
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Public Appearances, Series 5
  - The College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Ohlone and East Los Angeles colleges, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Southern Oregon State College, Ashland, Oregon, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Social Problems Seminar, Moses Lake, Washington (cancelled), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - US Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Washington D.C., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - San Diego City College, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Nutrition in Marketing Symposium, San Francisco, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Harnell College, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - East Los Angeles Community College, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Cousteau Interview, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Robert Aram Films, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Santa Barbara Community College, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Rally for Freedom of Choice, San Jose, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Australia, Folder 1 of 2, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Australia, Folder 2 of 2, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Daytona Beach Community College, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Seminar at Tucson, Arizona, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Henderson State University, Arkadelphia, Arkansas, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Clayton Junior College, Georgia, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Kennesaw Junior College, Georgia, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Gainsville Junior College, Georgia, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Interviews in San Francisco. Los Angeles, Chicago, and Detroit, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Interview on Iowa Public Radio, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Interview on CBS Atlanta, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Stanford Conference on Publishing, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - U.S. Department of State Program, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Interview on WKBD Detroit, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - KRON-TV San Francisco, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - University of Kansas, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Cornell University Seminar, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Yale University Seminar, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - The Costeau Society Seminar, Seattle, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - EDGE Course, Stanford, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Interview on WELI radio, New Haven, Connecticut, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Interview on WHLO radio, Akron, Ohio, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Fast for a World Harvest, Stanford, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Stanford Journal Club, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - New Frontiers in Pest Management, Sacramento, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Seattle appearances, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - University of Hawaii, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - UC Berkeley Seminar, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - The Population Institute, Los Angeles, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Institute for the Study of Human Knowledge, Washington D.C., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Cole Symposium, Cornell University, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - National Energy Conservation Challenge, Gunnison, Colorado, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Conference on Conservation Biology, UC San Diego, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Book Tour, Philadelphia, New York, Washington DC, Gainsville, FL, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Hardin Symposium, UC Santa Barbara, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Institute for the Study of Human Knowledge, San Francisco., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Tennessee Tech University, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - University of Northern Colorado, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Midwestern State University, Wichita Falls, Texas, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Stanford Alumni, Campus, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Book Tour, Dallas, Charlotte, NC, New York, Chicago, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Interviews in Los Angeles, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Stanford Alumni, Hawaii, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Mother Lode field trip Expense report, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - San Diego field trip Expense report, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Caribbean field trip Expense report, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Ebbetts Pass, California field trip Expense report, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Antarctica and Peru field trip Expense report, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - San Luis Obispo field trip Expense report, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sequoia Travel bills, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Stockholm Expense account, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Expenses other than research, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Expense reports, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Expense reports, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Expense reports, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Travel expenses, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Speech Schedules, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Donation letters of transmittal, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Donation letters of transmittal, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Itinerary May 20-30, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Travel schedules, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - American Program Bureau Southern Tour, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Mills College, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Expenses, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Speaking Schedules 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - SCOPE Conference, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Interview with Arthur Snyder, Family Circle magazine, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - The Allen Show, Los Angeles, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Topanga Center for Human Development, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Interview on KCET, Los Angeles, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Odetics Demonstration, Stanford, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Interview on WCAU-TV, Philadelphia, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Phoenix Executives Club, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - University of Kentucky, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - University of Texas, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Texas Tech University, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - C.W. Post College, Greenvale, New York, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The Tomorrow's People Show, CBS-TV, New York, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - The David Frost Show, CBS-TV, New York, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Fresno State College, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - WMAL-TV, Washington D.C., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Hartnell College, Salinas, California, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - The Tonight Show, NBC-TV, New York, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Interview with Netherlands Broadcasting and Television, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - BBC-TV film, Folder 1 of 2, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - BBC-TV film, Folder 2 of 2, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - International Congress of the American Marketing Association, San Francisco, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - The Ed Harvey Show, CBS radio, Philadelphia, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cabot College, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Meeting with Ralph Nader, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Elmhurst College, Illinois, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Wisconsin State University, Oshkosh, Wisconsin, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Wisconsin State University, Eau Claire, Wisconsin, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - St. Cloud State College, St. Cloud, Minnesota, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Telephone Interview, St. Louis Post-Dispatch, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Cross Films taping at KZSU, Stanford, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - American Society of Medical Technologists, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Population Commission Interview with Ralph Potter, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - CTV Interview at Stanford, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - United Nations film Interview at Stanford, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Stanford Business School, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - CBS-TV Interview with Allan Harper, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Australia, Africa, France, London tour, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Australia Trip preparations, Folder 1 of 2, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Australia Trip preparations, Folder 2 of 2, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Science Foundation for Physics, University of Sydney, Australia, Folder 1 of 3, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Science Foundation for Physics, University of Sydney, Australia, Folder 2 of 3, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Science Foundation for Physics, University of Sydney, Australia, Folder 3 of 3, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Seminars in Australia, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Fourth Australian Medical Congress, Brisbane, Australia, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Macquarie University, Australia, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Telephone Interview with London Daily Express, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Telephone Interview with Allan Goodall, Sydney Morning Herald, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Travel Preparations, Barbados, London, Nairobi, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - International Farm Youth Exchange, Ft. Collins, Colorado, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - The Tonight Show, NBC-TV, Los Angeles, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Marc Holzer, John Jay College, New York, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Interview with Pia Jensen, Femina Magazine, Denmark, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Proposition 9, California Environmental Initiative, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Interview with Owen Spann, KGO radion, San Francisco, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Common Cause Board Meeting, Washington D.C., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Earth Week, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - World Law Fund, Santa Cruz, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - NHK, Japanese Television, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Pre Fall Speaking Tour, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - University of Puget Sound, Tacoma, Washington, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - University of Tulsa, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Independent Natural Gas Association of America Annual Meeting, Puerto Rico, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Louisiana State University, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Orange Coast College, Costa Mesa, California, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - UC Davis, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Northern California Industrial Relations Council, San Francisco, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - UC Santa Barbara, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - American Program Bureau Tour, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Planned Parenthood, Santa Clara County, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Occidental College, Los Angeles, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - University of Missouri, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - University of Northern Colorado, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Eastern Kentucky University, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mercer University, Macon, Georgia, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Eastern Tennessee State University, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - University of South Florida, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - University of Florida, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - International Planned Parenthood Federation, Tokyo, Folder 1 of 2, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - International Planned Parenthood Federation, Tokyo, Folder 2 of 2, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Mitchel-Hutchins Seminar, New York, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - United Nations World Population Conference, Stockholm, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Washington University, St. Louis, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - World Wildlife Fund Congress, Bonn, Germany, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Ecolloquium, University of Leuven, Belgium, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Princeton University, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller University, New York, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - The Science Center, St. Petersburg, Florida, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Weber State University, Ogden, Utah, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - ZPG Miami, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Northwestern State University of Louisiana, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Associated Press Managing Editors Association, Louisville, Kentucky, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Kansas State University, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Cal Lutheran College, Thousand Oaks, California, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - ZPG Philadelphia, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - San Diego City College, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Expenses, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Publications, Series 6
  - Filming for the BBC, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rio Hondo Junior College, Whittier, California, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cal Poly at Pomona, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - University of Pacific, Stockton, California, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Conservation Group, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Valpariso College, Indiana, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The College Center of the Finger Lakes, Corning, New York, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - US National Commission for UNESCO, San Francisco, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Podium Circuit, Palo Alto, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - College of Marin, Kentfield, California, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - IBM Management Conference, San Francisco, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - "Hotline" show, KPIX-TV San Francisco, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - San Diego Open Forum, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - University of California San Diego, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - University of California Santa Barbara, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Channel City Club, Santa Barbara, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Planned Parenthood and AAUW, Livermore, California, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Stanford Medical Center Psychiatry Seminar, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - KSFO radio interview, San Francisco, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Population Explosion Conference, Stanford, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - IBM Technology and Culture Seminar, San Jose, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming 1969-1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming 1974, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming 1974, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming 1974, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jan-Mar 1975, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jan-Mar 1975, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jan-Mar 1975, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Apr-Jun 1975, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Apr-Jun 1975, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jul-Dec 1975, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jul-Dec 1975, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing Jan-Jun, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing Jul-Dec, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jan-Jun 1976,Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jan-Jun 1976, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jul-Dec 1976, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jul-Dec 1976, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing Jan-Jun, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing Jul-Dec, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jan-Jun 1977, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jan-Jun 1977, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jul-Dec, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming 1978, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming 1978, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence, Invitation Declined, Outgoing, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing Jan-Mar 1979, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing Jan-Mar 1979, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Apr-Jun 1979, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Apr-Jun 1979, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming Jul-Dec, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Incoming, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, Invitations Declined, Outgoing, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Article, A Food Glut in Our Future?, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Article, You Can't Win – Or Can You?, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Article, Hidden Effects of Overpopulation, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Article, Is Distribution the only Population Problem?, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Article, False Prophets of Doom, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Article, Dodging the Crisis, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Article, The Co-Evolutionary Race, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Article, Pollution and Population – How Strong the Link?, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Article, Who Makes the Babies?, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Article, Demographic Transition, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Article, The Heat Barrier, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Article, Population Control in the People's Republic of China, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Article, Abortion and Morality, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Article, Ecosystem Stability, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Article, Technology and Development, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Article, The Gypsy Moth Backlash, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Article, The Energy Crisis, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Article, Ecoside in Indochina, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Article, The "Lost Genius" Debate, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Article, One-Dimensional Ecology, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Article, One-Dimensional Ecology Revisited, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Article, Pollute Now – Pay Later, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Article, Fear of the Aged, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Article, Can We Wait for Proof?, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Article, The Lessons of the SST, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Article, The Food From the Sea Myth 1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Article, The Biological Evolution 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Article, The Population Explosion: Facts and Fiction, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Article, Birth Control: Too Little and Much Too Late, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Article, Hunger, Population, and the Facts of Life, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Article, Population and Environment 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Article, The Population Crisis, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Article, Are Americans Doomed?, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Article, How to Survive in an Age of Scarcity, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Article, The Coming Famine, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Article, The Population, Environment Crisis, Where do we stand now?, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Article, Our Environmental Crisis, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Article, Primer on Population Growth, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Article, Population Growth and the Future of Man, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Article, The Pie is Finite, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Article, A Biological View of Race 1964 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Article, Or is it a Time Bomb?, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Article, Blueprint for Survival, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Article, More on Forest Defoliation, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Article, Encyclical Protest, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Article, Book Review of "World Without Borders", 1972 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Article, Book Review of "Seeds of Change", 1969 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Article, Book Review of "Too Many", 1969 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Article for Rolling Stone Magazine, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bibliography for Ehrlich Articles, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Reprint and Errata Information 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Proof New Edition, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Update for New Edition, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Book, Population Bomb, English Edition 1972, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Book, Population Bomb, English Edition 1972, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Book, Population Bomb, English Edition 1972, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Book, Population Bomb, English Edition 1972, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Reviews 1968-1971, Folder 1 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Reviews 1968-1971, Folder 2 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Reviews 1968-1971, Folder 3 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Reviews 1968-1971, Folder 4 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Reviews 1968-1971, Folder 5 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Reviews 1968-1971, Folder 6 of 6 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Correspondence 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Book, Population Bomb, List of Gift Copies, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Errata 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Orders 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Illustration Suggestions, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Taping Excerpts, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Advertisements, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Revisions Suggestions 1968 -, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Publishing Correspondence 1971 –, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Correspondence 1968-1973, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Correspondence 1968-1973, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Correspondence 1968-1973, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Correspondence 1968-1973, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Correspondence from US Congressman and Senators 1969, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Book, Population Bomb, Correspondence from US Congressman and Senators 1969, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Books, Population, Resources, Environment (PREV) Comments and Corrections 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Books, PREV, Teachers Manual, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Books, PREV, Reviews, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Books, PREV, Reviews, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Books, PREV, Acknowledgements, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Books, PREV, Answers on Specific Questions 1970-1975, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Books, PREV, Answers on Specific Questions 1970-1975, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Books, PREV, Answers on Specific Questions 1970-1975, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Books, PREV, Answers on Specific Questions 1970-1975, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Books, PREV, WH Freeman & Co. 1969-1972, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Books, PREV, WH Freeman & Co. 1969-1972, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Books, PREV, WH Freeman & Co. 1969-1972, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Books, PREV, Correspondence 1970-1974, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Books, PREV, Correspondence 1970-1974, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Books, PREV, Bibliography, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Books, PREV, Publicity, Reviews 1970, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Books, PREV, Publicity, Reviews 1970, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Books, PREV, Publicity, Reviews 1970, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Books, PREV, Publicity, Reviews 1970, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - 3x5 cards listing Addresses (Box 3)
  - 3x5 cards listing reference books (Box 3)
  - 3x5 cards for "Title of Work in which Reprint will Appear" (Box 3)
  - 3x5 cards for "Title of Work to be Reprinted" (Box 3)
  - 3x5 cards for "Publisher of Work in which Article will be Reprinted" (Box 3)
  - 3x5 cards for "Publisher of Original Work (Rights)" (Box 3)
  - 3x5 cards for "Date Permission was Granted" (Box 3)
  - Books, The Process of Evolution, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Books, Permissions Granted 1974-1976, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Books, Permissions Granted 1974-1976, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Books, Permissions Paid, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Books, Permissions Free, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Books, Permissions Pending, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)